10/30/2018



jiho.lee.dev@gmail.com
http://jiholee.ml
Los Angeles, CA
(213) 935-7612





## **OBJECTIVE**

Full-stack developer from former designer. Experience designing and developing front-end and server-side small and large services. In a rapidly developing modern technology environment, always keep trying to learn and understand the flow of new technology. Regardless of platform, able to quickly learn and apply a variety of technologies.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Nov 2010 - Present

**Freelancer** Developer

Los Angeles California

B2B e-commerce market place with CMS WordPress on AWS

Nov 2008 - Sep 2010

**Wewelcom** Web Developer

Anyang-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea

e-commerce solution ASP, MSSQL, API with SOAP and XML

Aug 2005 - Nov 2008

**SEJONG Telecom (Ex. Onse Telecom)** Web Developer

Seongnam, Gyeonggi-do, Korea

MRO IIS, ASP, MSSQL, Oracle, COM+ Sockets, MFC, C#.Net, Ajax

Mar 2004 - Aug 2005 Assistant Engineer

SI business, signal simulator, UI Design, PDA app, Mobile 2003

Jan 2002 - Mar 2004

**Seil I&C** Designer & Developer

Gwanak-gu, Seoul, Korea

Designed and Developed branding websites web apps on LAMP

# **TECHNIQUES**

#### Front-End

HTML5, CSS3, Saas, Less Javascript, ES6, TypeScript Bootstrap, Foundation JQuery, Vue.js, React, js

#### **Back-End**

PHP, ASP, JSP, C#.NET, Laravel MSSQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL NoSQL: MongoDB, MariaDB Node.js, APIs, DevOps, Git, JIRA Cloud: AWS, Azure, GCP

#### **CMS**

WordPress, Drupal, Joomla!, XE3, WooCommerce, Magento, Orchard, Umbrac

## Apps

Swift, Object-C, Java, NW.js Cordova, CocoaPods, Xamarin Vue Native, React Native, Ionic

### **EDUCATION**

Mar 2015 - Sep 2018

**Pacific States University** 

Bachelor of Science, C.I.S

Los Angeles California

Jan 2011 - Mar 2015

Santa Monica College

AS, Computer Programming
Santa Monica California

Feb 2001 - Jan 2003

**Hoseo University** 

Dropout, Information and Telecommunication Engineering